radioandrecords.com 2009-04-26

# Welcome to Radio and Records

**PRIVACY POLICY & USERS RIGHTS**  
  
This site is part of The Nielsen Company network of web sites.

At The Nielsen Company we take your privacy very seriously. Because of this we want to provide you with explicit information on how we collect, gather, and identify information during your visit to our site. This information may be expanded or updated as we change or develop our site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time-to-time to see if anything has changed. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of our privacy policy.  
Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email or postal address. In many cases we need this information to provide the personalized or enhanced service that you have requested.

The amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose to The Nielsen Company is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us in conjunction with one of our services.

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?  
**  
The Nielsen Company collects information on our users in three ways: by your voluntary submissions (for instance, if you sign up for one of our email newsletters) and/or surveys; sweepstakes and/or contest entries; and through cookie technology.

In our effort to provide personalization and opportunities for prizes and services, we may at times ask you to submit information such as your name or email address, or to share your interests and hobbies with us. You never have to answer these questions, and you can decline this exchange of information on any site on the Internet - not just ours - at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information, such as a personalized stock portfolio, a sweepstakes entry, or the purchase and shipment of products and prizes to people who visit our network.

The information The Nielsen Company collects is used in a variety of ways: for internal review; to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; to notify you about updates to the service; and to let you know about products and services that you may be interested in.

Email: If you have provided us your email address, The Nielsen Company periodically sends promotional emails to its subscribers about services offered by The Nielsen Company and its partners. If you do not wish to receive email information from The Nielsen Company, please let us know by emailing us at: [rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com](mailto:rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com) or by writing us at Radio & Records, Inc.,   
5055 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 600, Los Angeles, CA 90036.

The "email this article" feature is an easy way for you to send articles through email. The email addresses that you supply to use this service will not be used for any other purpose without your consent.  
**  
With whom does The Nielsen Company share the information it gathers/tracks?  
**  
From time to time we share this information with other reputable organizations for marketing purposes or the information is used by The Nielsen Company to contact consumers for its own marketing endeavors. As a valued consumer, we offer you the opportunity to "opt out," or request not to accept these marketing opportunities. If at any time you change your mind and do not want The Nielsen Company to share your email address or home address with other companies and/or organizations, or would simply like to be removed from the list, please let us know by emailing us at rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com or by writing us at Radio & Records, Inc., 5055 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 600, Los Angeles, CA 90036.

**Sweepstakes/Contests  
**  
From time-to-time The Nielsen Company, along with other reputable companies, provides sweepstakes and other contests for the enjoyment of our users. By participating in the contest or sweepstakes and answering any and all questions, the user understands that The Nielsen Company and/or the involved company(s) may use the information obtained for marketing purposes. Children under 18 may not participate in any sweepstakes or contest promoted by The Nielsen Company.

**Cookies  
**  
The Nielsen Company may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information and data through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files a Web site uses to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to the site and facilitate the use of the site. "Cookies" also allow a site to track usage behavior and compile site usage information that will allow for the improvement of content and target advertising.   
**  
About Children's Privacy  
**  
The Nielsen Company is committed to the safety of our children. Children under 18 may not participate in any sweepstakes or contests on The Nielsen Company. Also, we encourage children under the age of 18 to ask a parent for permission before providing or sending any information to anyone online.  
**  
Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy by The Nielsen Company. Once again, if you do not wish us to share this information with other reputable companies that we think you might be interested in, please let us know by emailing us at rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com. 

**Questions?**

We welcome your questions and/or comments. Please send all queries to [rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com. ](mailto:rrwebmaster@radioandrecords.com)
